(Stuart:)Anyway,
so what do I got to do to-to
(Stuart:)get you in
the door?
(Amy:)Well, for starters,
(Amy:)you might want to rethink
some of this artwork.
(Amy:)I mean, this woman's
actually on a leash like a dog.
(Stuart:)Well, you don't know
the backstory.
(Stuart:)Maybe she kept jumping up
on the couch.
(Raj:)I feel cool.
(Raj:)Like Puss in Boots.
(Leonard:)I always wanted to be
a swashbuckler when I was a kid.
(Sheldon:)Technically,
"swashbuckler" is a combination
of two terms.
"Swash" referring to the sound
of the sword.
(Leonard:)Swash.
(Howard:)And
then
"buckler" meaning a small
shield, which you don't have.
(Raj:)We can still be swashers.
Hmm.
(Howard:)Well said, Puss.
(Barry:)Gentlemen, welcome
to the fencing club.